narendramodi.in 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Home | www.narendramodi.in

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.narendramodi.in/privacy-policy/)

We believe in offering complete confidentiality to those visiting our website. The Privacy Policy of the website respects your privacy and thus precisely put forth the manner in which your data is collected and used by this website.

You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully before going ahead with any activity on our website.

**Personal Information:**

• When you register, you will be asked to provide your personal information. The information we collect will not be shared with any  
other website or application. It will only be used by this website.  
• This application uses cookies and other techniques to keep a record of your interactions which you have had with the website in  
the past. This is done only to offer a personalized experience.

In the process, we may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:  
• Your name including first and last name  
• Your username while login via 3rd party websites  
• Your alternate email address  
• Your mobile phone number and contact details  
• Your ZIP/Postal code  
• Your demographic profile (i.e. your age, gender, occupation, & address)  
• Your preferences and interests (such as news, sports & travel among others)  
• Your opinions on features on our website

We may also collect the following information:  
• About the pages you visit or access  
• Links you visit on our website  
• Number of times you access the page

**Exchanging Information to/from Facebook & Twitter:**

• When you choose to login either via Facebook or Twitter, we collect your personal information from these respective websites  
and use it only for authentication and display purpose.  
• This information we collect is not shared with any other websites or applications and is only used by and within this website.
